## Sean Chaucer Levine

(908-285-5179) sean@ghostmouth.com Minneapolis, MN

Experienced Web Developer, Educator, and Audio Engineer with great communication skills. Excels at debugging, team oriented full stack web development, and front-end design. Obsessed with troubleshooting, digesting new information, and creating iconic content. Knowledgeable and experienced at implementing a variety of different database languages, and a proficient performer and educator of over twelve musical instruments.

Portfolio: http://www.seanchaucerlevine.com

*LinkedIn*: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sean-levine-a803a239/

Github: https://github.com/Ghostmouth

## Technical Skills

- Computer Technologies: Javascript, Java, Swift, React.js, Angular.js, jQuery, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, Express, Firebase, MySQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, AWS, AJAX, Python, PHP, Git
- Audio Workstations: Logic Pro, Protools, Ableton Live, Harrison Mixbus, Reaper
- Visual Editing Suites: Photoshop, ImageGlitch, iMovie, Microsoft Office
- Musical Instruments: Piano, Trumpet, Trombone, Flute, Guitar, Saxophone, Synthesizer, Percussion, Upright and Electric Bass, Clarinet, Ukulele, Harmonica, Mandolin, Banjo, Violin, Drum Set, Voice

# **Projects**

<Boot-Connect> (Job Board) | https://github.com/JasonErdahl/boot-connect |
https://boot-connect.herokuapp.com/
React, AWS, Authentication, Front End

Integrates a SQL database with a task management database to store user information, project information, tasks, and deadlines. Utilizes mySQL, JavaScript, React.js, jQuery, Sequelize, HTML5, CSS, AWS, multer, passport.JS, node.JS, and Express.

New York Times News Scraper | <a href="https://github.com/Ghostmouth/newsscraper">https://github.com/Ghostmouth/newsscraper</a> | <a href="https://mongoose-hwassignment.herokuapp.com/">https://mongoose-hwassignment.herokuapp.com/</a> | Full Stack Development

Scrapes news articles from New York Times, with functionality to save and store articles, and comments to a mongo database. Utilizes React.js, mongoDB, mongoose, JavaScript, handlebars, HTML, CSS, and node.js.

Band Website | <a href="https://github.com/Ghostmouth/ghostmouthwebsite">https://github.com/Ghostmouth/ghostmouthwebsite</a> | <a href="https://www.ghostmouth.com">https://github.com/Ghostmouth/ghostmouthwebsite</a> | <a href="https://www.ghostmouth.com">https://www.ghostmouth.com</a> | Full Stack Development

Website for a Minneapolis music project. Utilizes JavaScript, handlebars, HTML, and CSS.

# Professional Experience

## Minneapolis Public Schools- Reserve Teacher

September 2017-Present

• Implemented a variety of different curriculums and lesson plans for elementary, middle, and high school teachers at many schools in the Minneapolis Public School district

#### Teachers On Call- Reserve Teacher

January 2016- Present

 Assisted in the learning process for special needs students in the 916 District, Hopkins, and St. Paul School Systems, with particular focus on schools that specialize in Emotional Behavior Disorders, and Autism

## Cause Spirits and Soundbar-Web Developer

Spring 2012- July 2014

- Updated, maintained, and debugged the venue's website
- Implemented a SQL database for the venue's event calendar, with a PHP backend
- Integrated the website with the venue's various social media pages
- Advised the management of the venue on how to increase the establishment's search engine optimization

## Banana Static-Web Manager, Public Relations

January 2010- June 2012

- Developed, designed, and maintained the website for a Minneapolis Entertainment Web Site that saw some popularity as a music review site
- Maintained email contact and accepted submissions from various publishing companies, record labels, and management teams
- Contributed content to the website

## 331 Club- Security Professional

Spring 2013- Present

- In charge of managing and training the security staff of the club, ensuring the safety of the staff, and patrons during a variety of different of events that the club hosted
- Assisted in the management the security team during the Art-A-Whirl event of 2013, 2014, 2015, 2016, 2017, and 2018

## Education

University of Minnesota- Certificate in Web Development

McNally Smith College of Music- Bachelor of Music in Performance